[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1986, this diamond found in a South African mine beat the record for the worlds largest faceted diamond.", "correct_answer": "Golden Jubilee", "incorrect_answers": ["Second Star of Africa", "Great Star of Africa", "Centtenary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the popular final words of gangster Rico in the 1930 crime movie Little Caesar?", "correct_answer": "Mother of mercy, is this the end of Rico?", "incorrect_answers": ["Holy cow, is that a gun youre holding right there?", "For Christs sake, shoot me like a man!", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Perfect Storm, what is the name of The Andrea Gails sister boat, captained by Linda Greenlaw, played by actress Mary Elizabeth Mastrantonio?", "correct_answer": "The Hannah Boden", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cecile", "The Big Red", "The Gloucester Girl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It can be shown that this President is related, either by blood or by marriage, to eleven other Presidents.", "correct_answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamin Harrison", "James Madison", "Teddy Roosevelt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the classic movie Home Alone first hit the theatres in the United States?", "correct_answer": "1990", "incorrect_answers": ["1991", "1992", "1993"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is the Spotted wobbegong?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Reptile", "Amphibian", "Marsupial"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scrabble, an amusing family game created by architect Alfred Mosher Butts in 1938, is what type of game?", "correct_answer": "Word game", "incorrect_answers": ["Dare game", "Chance game", "Athletic game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of books are called novela rosa, or pink novel, in Spain?", "correct_answer": "Sentimental novels", "incorrect_answers": ["Crime novels", "Erotic novels", "Books for little children"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first US police force to buy a police car was also the first to have a police motorcycle squad.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Topic: X-Men: This mutant has the ability to teleport. He has blue skin and a tail. His nickname is Nightcrawler. What is the right question?", "correct_answer": "Who is Kurt Wagner?", "incorrect_answers": ["Who is Eric Lensherr?", "Who is Scott Summers?", "Who is Bobby Drake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Web pages can be viewed on which of these devices?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cell phone", "PDA", "Personal Computer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what date was the movie Lean on Me released?", "correct_answer": "March 3, 1989", "incorrect_answers": ["April 3, 1989", "February 3, 1989", "May 3, 1989"]}]